Finding Aid for the W.W. Robinson papers, ca. 1843-1972
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Research material: Abstracts of title - city, rancho properties.
  - Ranchos, Los Angeles County.
    - San Pasqual.
      - [No compiler given].
        - Abstract of title of that certain real property in the Rancho San Pasqual., 1886 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - San Pedro.
      - Galloway and Lienau.
        - Abstract of title of the following property situate in the County of Los Angeles, State of California particularly described as follows, to wit: Being lots number two and five in Block A of the Rancho San Pedro., 1884 (Box 73, Folder 3)
          1 v. In paper boards
    - San Pedro (Inner Bay, Rattlesnake Island, Salt Flats).
      - Lee and Scott.
        - Report and opinion on title of Ana Josefa Dominguez de Guyerto those portions of the Rancho San Pedro, situated in the county of Los Angeles, State of California, known as "Rattlesnake Island",. (Box 73, Folder 5)
          1 v. In black cloth
      - Los Angeles Terminal R'y Co.
        - Patent to Rancho San pedro., ca. 1892 (Box 73, Folder 4)
        - Abstract of title and certificate of search to all of that certain tract of land situate in the County of Los Angeles, State of California, described as follows: at a point on the exterior boundary of the Rancho San Pedro., ca. 1892 (Box 74, Folder 1)
        - Abstract of title to that real property., ca. 1892 (Box 74, Folder 2)
          V. 2. Bound in half leather
        - [Taxes and wharf franchise]., ca. 1892 (Box 74, Folder 3)
          V. 5. Bound in half leather
        - [Index]., ca. 1892 (Box 74, Folder 4)
          Bound in half leather
    - San Rafael.
      - [No compiler given].
        - Abstract of title of that certain real property in the County of Los Angeles, State of California, bounded and described as follows: The interest of Ralph Rogers in the Garavanza lands., 1887 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - San Rafael (Verdugo Ranch).
      - The Abstract Title Insurance Co.
        - [Rancho San Rafael]., 1893 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - San Vincente y Santa Monica.
      - [No compiler given].
        - San Vincente y Santa Monica, Boca de Santa Monica, Potrero de Santa Monica as to the interest acquired by Robert S. Baker and John P. Jones., 1933? (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Santa Anita.
      - The Abstract Title Insurance Co. of Los Angeles, Cal.
        - Abstract of title --- that portion of the Rancho Santa Anita which lies within the boundaries of the tract described on page 169 hereof and also within the boundaries., 1892? (Box 75, Folder 4)
          1 v. Bound in half leather (damaged)
      - The Abstract and Title Insurance Co.
        - Abstract of title of thatportion of the Rancho Santa Anita., 1892 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Santa Catalina Island.
      - [No compiler given].
        - Abstract of title to that certain real property situate in the county of Los Angeles, State of California and known as the island of Santa Catalina., 1891 (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - Santa Gertrudes.
      - Los Angeles Abstract Co.
        - Abstract of title to that real property situated in the County of Los Angelesknown as the J.W. Hellman Tract of the Colima Tract of the Santa Gertrude. (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - Simi.
      - [No compiler given].
        - [Rancho Simi]., CHECK DATE (Box 75, Folder 7)
        - Index to Simi Rancho., ca. 1919? (Box 75, Folder 7)
          1 v. In wrappers (cover missing)
    - Tajauta.
      - [Probate court].
        - Office abstract of Rancho Tajauta or Los Cuervos., ca. 1874 (Box 76, Folder 1)
          1 v. In marble boards, cloth spine
      - Abstract of title of that certain real property in the County of.
        - Los Angeles, State of California, bounded and described as follows: Rancho Tajauta or Los Cuervos., 1892 (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Tujunga.
      - [No compiler given].
        - Abstract of title of that certain real property in the Rancho Tujunga., 1892 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Ranchos, Sacramento County.
    - Del Paso.
      - Buckley - Gerber Abstract and Title Co.
        - [Rancho Del Paso]., 1910 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Ranchos, San Bernardino County.
    - Muscupiabe.
      - [No compiler given].
        - Abstract of title of the following described properly, situate in the County of San Bernardino, State of California., 1893 (Box 76, Folder 4)
          V. 1 of 2. Bound in half leather
      - Consolidated Abstract and Title Guaranty Co.
        - [Muscupiabe]., 1893 (Box 76, Folder 5)
          V. 2 of 2. Bound in half leather
  - Ranchos, Santa Barbara County.
    - Dos Pueblos.
      - Santa Barbara Abstract and Guaranty Company Co.
        - Abstract of title to all that certain real property situate, lying and being in the County of Santa Barbaraa part of the Rancho Dos Pueblos., 1923 (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - San Julian.
      - [No compiler given].
        - Abstract of title to San Julian Rancho, vol. 4., 1894 (Box 77, Folder 2)
          1 v. Map of the Rancho
      - Santa Barbara Abstract and Title Co.
        - Abstract of title to all that certain real property situated in the County of Santa Barbarabeing the Rancho San Julian, part of Rancho Las Cruces, Co., showing their division into tracts A, B C., 1907 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Ranchos, Ventura County.
    - Las Posas.
      - [No compiler given].
        - Abstract of title as to the interest of the heirs of Francisco Antonio de la Guerrain and to the Rancho De Las Posas., 1919 (Box 78, Folder 1)
- Research material: Land articles, rancho lists, etc.
  - City Properties, Los Angeles County.
    - Redondo Villa Tract.
      - Publications / articles.
        - Memo from W. H. Allen to WWR; concerns Redondo Villa Tract brochure., 1953 (Box 87, Folder 9)
          1 item, 1 pc. Also envelope. Brochure not here
    - Rosecrans Township.
      - Publications / articles.
        - Newspaper clipping., 1949 (Box 86, Folder 33)
        - [Rosecrans 'rancho' information]., 1949 (Box 87, Folder 18)
    - San Gabriel.
      - Publications / articles.
        - Copy of document., No dates / various dates (Box 87, Folder 19)
          3 leaves. Typescript (carbon)
        - Carmen Moreno de Abila plat., No date (Box 87, Folder 20)
        - WWR's notes., No dates / various dates (Box 87, Folder 21)
        - Purcell property at San Gabriel., No date (Box 87, Folder 22)
          2 leaves. Typescript (carbon) with holograph additions
        - Purcell property at San Gabriel., No date (Box 87, Folder 23)
          2 leaves. Typescript with extensive holograph additions
  - City Properties, Santa Barbara County.
    - Santa Maria.
      - Publications / articles.
        - Clipping., 1951 Jul (Box 86, Folder 34)
  - County Properties, Santa Barbara County.
    - Santa Barbara Ranchos.
      - Publications / articles.
        - Chart of grantees, acreage, etc., No dates / various dates (Box 86, Folder 31)
          1 folded leaf. Photocopy?
        - Rancho life and fiesta days. Newspaper clippings., 1940, 1957 (Box 86, Folder 32)
  - Ranchos.
    - "Romance of the Ranchos".
      - Publications / articles.
        - 2 cop., No date (Box 88, Folder 17)
          12p. WWR's involvement not known. Cf. items in T.I.T. segments, Box ____
    - Conner, E. Palmer. The Romance of the Ranchos.
      - Publications / articles.
        - Copy., 1929? (Box 88, Folder 9)
          40p. illus., fold. map. 18 cm. Los Angeles, Title Insurance and Trust Company. With author's autograph on title page
        - Another copy., No dates / various dates (Box 88, Folder 10)
          With some holograph changes, evidently for new edition
        - Another copy., No dates / various dates (Box 88, Folder 11)
          With extensive holograph notes and corrections. Note on inserted leaf: 1st proof. Dr. Perry Worden's corrected copy. Copy for 2nd edition
        - Another copy. Fourth edition., No dates / various dates (Box 88, Folder 12)
        - Another copy. Sixth edition., No dates / various dates (Box 88, Folder 13)
        - Another copy. Reprinting in a different format. 2 cop., 1939? (Box 88, Folder 14)
          illus., fold. color map, 23 cm. With illustrative drawings rather than photographs
        - Another copy., No dates / various dates (Box 88, Folder 15)
          Wrappers salmon, rather than light brown; or were others faded
    - General.
      - Publications / articles.
        - Sale / development of large rancho properties. Newspaper clippings., 1912 - 1965 (Box 86, Folder 1)
        - Rancho life. Clippings. (Box 86, Folder 2)
        - Letters from the Bancroft Library concerning Mexican land grant records., 1962, 1971 (Box 87, Folder 1)
          4 items, 4 pcs
        - WWR's notes., No dates / various dates (Box 87, Folder 10)
          13 leaves. Holograph. 1 leaf not in WWR's hand
        - WWR's notes., No dates / various dates (Box 87, Folder 11)
          42 leaves. Holograph
        - WWR's and IBR's holograph lists of California ranchos., No dates / various dates (Box 87, Folder 24)
          2 notebooks
        - WWR: The Ranchos of California., No dates / various dates (Box 87, Folder 25)
          50 leaves. Typescript (carbon)
        - WWR: The Ranchos of California., No dates / various dates (Box 87, Folder 26)
          51 leaves. Typescript
        - WWR: The Ranchos of California., No dates / various dates (Box 87, Folder 27)
          51 leaves. Typescript (carbon) with holograph corrections
        - WWR: The Ranchos of California., No dates / various dates (Box 87, Folder 28)
          51 leaves. Typescript (carbon)
        - [Ranchos by county]., No dates / various dates (Box 88, Folder 1)
          99 leaves. Typescript (carbon). A draft of previous rancho lists?
        - [Notes on ranchos: grantees, histories, etc]., No dates / various dates (Box 88, Folder 2)
          87 leaves. Holograph
        - [Notes on ranchos: grantees, histories, etc]., No dates / various dates (Box 88, Folder 3)
          300 leaves. Typescript with holograph corrections (photocopy). Note cards of WWR now photocopied; cards disposed of except for those in following folder
        - [Notes on ranchos: grantees, histories, etc] Not used for lists?., No dates / various dates (Box 88, Folder 4)
          On note cards. Typescript with holograph corrections
        - [Notes on ranchos: grantees, histories, etc]., No dates / various dates (Box 88, Folder 5)
          On note cards. Typescript with extensive holograph corrections. Samples kept to show WWR's working method, and for exhibit purposes
    - Highlights on Romance of the Ranchos.
      - Publications / articles.
        - No title., No date (Box 88, Folder 16)
          25 leaves. Typescript (carbon). Note on first leaf: L. Otis
  - Ranchos, Los Angeles County.
    - Aguaje de Centinela.
      - Publications / articles.
        - Newspaper clipping., 1950 (Box 86, Folder 3)
        - Correspondence and notes., 1965 (Box 87, Folder 2)
          3 items, 3 pcs. Ella Cole to WWR. Mimeographed letter from Elizabeth Carr to Ella Cole. Information about owners of the ranchos before Daniel Freeman WWR's notes
    - Boca de Santa Monica.
      - Publications / articles.
        - Magazine clipping., 1948 Oct (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - El Escorpion.
      - Publications / articles.
        - Newspaper clippings., 1957 - 1958 (Box 86, Folder 5)
        - WWR's notes., No dates / various dates (Box 87, Folder 12)
    - La Brea.
      - Publications / articles.
        - Newspaper clipping., 1962 (Box 86, Folder 6)
    - La Puente.
      - Publications / articles.
        - Newspaper clippings., 1949 - 1950 (Box 86, Folder 7)
    - Los Alamitos.
      - Publications / articles.
        - Letters from Katherine B. Hotchkis., 1964 and no date (Box 86, Folder 8)
        - Bixby, Katharine Hotchkis. Rancho Los Alamitos. Balboa, California, 1964., No dates / various dates (Box 86, Folder 9)
          2 cop. Enclosures to above. Verso title page: For W.W. Robinson, the indisputable authority on Southern California history, Katherine Bixby Hotchkis
        - Printed ephemera., 1964 (Box 86, Folder 10)
          Postcard, printed brochure with map, etc
        - Newspaper clippings., 1964, 1966 (Box 86, Folder 11)
    - Los Cerritos.
      - Publications / articles.
        - Note from Alice Titus, enclosing brochure., 1955 (Box 86, Folder 12)
          Los Cerritos Rancho House
    - Los Coyotes.
      - Publications / articles.
        - Newspaper clippings., 1945 (Box 86, Folder 13)
    - Los Feliz.
      - Publications / articles.
        - Newspaper clippings., 1949 (Box 86, Folder 14)
        - Letters., 1946 (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - Los Nietos.
      - Publications / articles.
        - Letter to WWR from A.L. Rhodes., 1935 (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - Los Nietos and Santa Gertrudes Rancho Section of los Nietos.
      - Publications / articles.
        - Newspaper clipping., 1956 Apr (Box 86, Folder 15)
    - Los Palos Verdes.
      - Publications / articles.
        - Newspaper clipping., 1955 and no date (Box 86, Folder 16)
        - 2/22 Patents [Report of survey of Rancho Los Palos Verdes]. Copy., 1880 (Box 87, Folder 14)
          25 leaves. Typescript
        - Proceedings leading up to confirmation of Rancho Los Palos Verdes., No dates / various dates (Box 87, Folder 15)
    - Potrero de Felipe Lugo.
      - Publications / articles.
        - Newspaper clippings., 1949, no date (Box 86, Folder 17)
    - Providencia.
      - Publications / articles.
        - WWR's holograph notes., No dates / variuos dates (Box 87, Folder 13)
    - Rincon de los Bueyes.
      - Publications / articles.
        - Romance of a rancho. In: The Beverly Hills Citizen., 1939 Jun 23 (Box 86, Folder 18)
          Features, v. 17 no. 2, p. [1], 6. Article is unsigned, but note gives credit to W.W. Robinson, among others
    - Rodeo de las Aguas.
      - Publications / articles.
        - The story of El Rancho Rodeo de las Aguas. In: The Southland Federal news., 1953 Oct (Box 86, Folder 19)
    - San Antonio.
      - Publications / articles.
        - Program for the marking of the historic Casa de Rancho San Antonio., 1946 Mar (Box 86, Folder 20)
        - Letters from WWR to A.J. Gray. (Box 87, Folder 5)
          2 items, 2 pcs. Give brief history of rancho
    - San Jose.
      - Publications / articles.
        - Newspaper clipping., 1938 (Box 86, Folder 21)
    - San Jose de Buenos Ayres.
      - Publications / articles.
        - [Rancho histories] In: Westwood Hills Press., 1947 Apr 17 (Box 86, Folder 22)
          Contains: The story of the Spanish ranchos by Florence Backus; and Westwood Hills eulogized by late poet laureate John Steven McGroaty
    - San Pedro.
      - Publications / articles.
        - Newspaper clipping., No date (Box 86, Folder 23)
    - San Rafael.
      - Publications / articles.
        - Newspaper clipping., 1929 (Box 86, Folder 24)
        - WWR's notes., No dates / various dates (Box 87, Folder 16)
        - Copies of documents., No dates / various dates (Box 87, Folder 17)
    - Simi.
      - Publications / articles.
        - Outlaws of Santa Susana Pass., 1953 Apr 1 (no. 4) and 1954 Oct 15 (no. 6) (Box 86, Folder 25)
          Mimeographed newsletters with articles on topics concerned with Rancho Simi
        - Photograph of Camulos chapel., No dates / various dates (Box 86, Folder 26)
          Removed from previous publication
        - Letter to WWR from Florence ____., No date (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - Ranchos, Riverside County.
    - General.
      - Publications / articles.
        - Casa Loma. Newspaper clipping., 1962 (Box 86, Folder 27)
    - Santa Rosa.
      - Publications / articles.
        - Clipping., 1949 Jan (Box 86, Folder 28)
  - Ranchos, San Diego County.
    - General.
      - Publications / articles.
        - [Histories] In: The southern California rancher., 1941 - 1966 (Box 86, Folder 29)
          Histories of various ranches and ranchos
  - Ranchos, San Francisco County.
    - San Francisco Bay Ranchos.
      - Publications / articles.
        - Booklist marked by WWR., No date (Box 86, Folder 30)
  - Ranchos, Santa Barbara County.
    - General.
      - Publications / articles.
        - Correspondence., 1965 Oct, 1966 May - Jun (Box 87, Folder 7)
          4 items, 5 pcs. Also WWR's notes from envelope. Includes letter from: Don Meadows
        - WWR's notes., No dates / various dates (Box 88, Folder 6)
          5 leaves. Holograph
        - Index cards of ranchos., No dates / various dates (Box 88, Folder 7)
          44 pieces. Holograph
  - Ranchos, Ventura County.
    - San Francisco.
      - Publications / articles.
        - WWR's letters to Phil Townsend Hanna and R.W. Gray., 1949 Jul (Box 87, Folder 8)
- Robinson, Irene Bowen.
  - IV. Juvenile Books and Stories.
    - General.
      - post publication material.
        - Kern County Book Fair correspondence., 1963 (Box 130, Folder 25)
- Robinson, Irene Bowen. Papers: personal and art related.
  - Art.
    - Artists' Protest Exhibition.
      - Exhibit catalogs.
        - Copy / Copies., 1945 (Box 131, Folder 6)
          Protests selection policies for L.A. County Museum's 1st Biennial Exhibition of Drawings, 1945. Includes - Ernst, Dorthea Tanning, Lipchitz, Zadkine
    - California Art Club.
      - Exhibit catalogs.
        - Copy / Copies., 1924 -1939 (Box 131, Folder 7)
          no. 15-18, 20-24, 26-27 and California Art Club, opening exhibition - Barnsdale Park, 1927.
    - California State Fair.
      - Exhibit catalogs.
        - Copy / Copies., 1929, 1933 - 1935 (Box 131, Folder 8)
    - California Water Color Society.
      - Exhibit catalogs.
        - Copy / Copies., 1926 - 1956 (Box 131, Folder 9)
          Pasadena Art Institute, Santa Barbara Museum of Art, Los Angeles County Museum
        - Copy / Copies., No date (Box 131, Folder 10)
          Exhbition and Sale of water colors May 5th to 31st
        - Copy / Copies., 1929 (Box 131, Folder 11)
        - Copy / Copies., 1939 - 1940, 1944, 1946, 1948 (Box 131, Folder 12)
        - Copy / Copies., 1934 (Box 131, Folder 13)
    - Chaffey, Ontario, California.
      - Exhibit catalogs.
        - Copy / Copies., 1942, 1944 - 1945 (Box 131, Folder 14)
          no. 2, 4 - 5
    - Christmas Cards.
      - Samples.
        - Some with names of others., No dates (Box 132, Folder 31)
          Fay and Lawrence Clark Powell, etc
    - City of Los Angeles Art Exhibition.
      - Exhibit catalogs.
        - Copy / Copies., 1948 - 1951 (Box 131, Folder 15)
          no. 4 - 7
    - Ebell Salon of Art.
      - Exhibit catalogs.
        - Copy / Copies., 1930 - 1950 (inclusive) (Box 131, Folder 16)
          no. 1 -
    - Fine Arts Gallery of San Diego.
      - Exhibit catalogs.
        - Copy / Copies., 1926 - 1940 (Box 131, Folder 30)
          no. 1 - 3, 5 - 8, 11 - 12
    - Fine Arts Society of San Diego, California.
      - Exhibit catalogs.
        - Copy / Copies., 1941 (Box 131, Folder 17)
    - Foundation of Western Art.
      - Exhibit catalogs.
        - Copy / Copies., 1935 - 1937, 1941, 1942, 1944 (Box 131, Folder 18)
        - Copy / Copies., 1936 - 1939, 1943 (Box 131, Folder 19)
    - Gardena High School.
      - Exhibit catalogs.
        - Copy / Copies., 1928, 1929 - 1930, 1934 - 1935, and no date (Box 131, Folder 20)
          no. 2 - 5, 7
    - General.
      - Exhibit material, etc.
        - Bibliographical notes, catalog information., 1946, no date (Box 131, Folder 2)
          1946 is for exhibit at Glendale Public Library
    - General Materials.
      - Ephemera.
        - Membership cards., 1947, 1971 (Box 131, Folder 1)
    - Laguna Beach Art Association.
      - Exhibit catalogs.
        - Copy / Copies., 1928, 1929 - 1930, 1934 - 1935, and no date (Box 131, Folder 21)
    - Los Angeles Art Association.
      - Exhibit catalogs.
        - Copy / Copies., 1934 (Box 131, Folder 22)
          no. 1
        - Copy / Copies., 1941 (Box 131, Folder 23)
    - Los Angeles County Fair.
      - Exhibit catalogs.
        - Copy / Copies., 1928, 1934, 1936-1939, 1948 (Box 131, Folder 31)
          catalogues no. 7, 13, 15 and years 1937-1939, n.d.
    - Los Angeles County Museum.
      - Exhibit documentation.
        - "The dove." Photograph., 1954 (Box 131, Folder 5)
          Note on verso: honorable mention in watercolors
      - No subsubseries.
        - Copy / Copies., 1943 (Box 131, Folder 29)
          1 folded leaf. Brief biography and description of subjects and styles. No illus
    - Los Angeles Museum.
      - Exhibit catalogs.
        - Copy / Copies., 1927, 1928, 1930 - 1935, 1938 (Box 131, Folder 24)
        - Copy / Copies., 1940, 1945 and 1957 (Box 131, Folder 25)
          no. 1, no. 17?, 20?
        - Copy / Copies., 1938 February (Box 131, Folder 26)
        - Copy / Copies., 1929 (Box 131, Folder 28)
    - Los Angeles Museum of History and Science.
      - Exhibit catalogs.
        - Copy / Copies., 1922 - 1923, 1926 (Box 131, Folder 27)
          no. 3 - 4, 7
    - Los Angeles Public Library.
      - Exhibit catalogs.
        - Copy / Copies., 1931, no date (Box 132, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous Sketches.
      - Samples.
        - On tracing paper, etc., No dates (Box 132, Folder 30)
          Seemingly minor
    - National Orange Show.
      - Exhibit catalogs.
        - Copy / Copies., 1949, 1951, 1955 (Box 132, Folder 2)
          no. 34, 36, 40
    - Palos Verdes Community Arts Association.
      - Exhibit catalogs.
        - Copy / Copies., No date (Box 132, Folder 3)
    - Palos Verdes Public Library and Art Gallery.
      - Exhibit catalogs.
        - Copy / Copies., 1930 - 1931 (Box 132, Folder 4)
          no. 1 - 2
    - Pasadena Art Institute.
      - Exhibit catalogs.
        - Copy / Copies., 1930, 1932, Fall Opening - 1946 Oct (Box 132, Folder 5)
          no. 3, 5
    - Progressive Painters of Southern California.
      - Exhibit catalogs.
        - Copy / Copies., No date (Box 132, Folder 6)
        - Copy / Copies., 1933 (Box 132, Folder 7)
        - Copy / Copies., 1933 (Box 132, Folder 8)
        - Copy / Copies., 1934 (Box 132, Folder 9)
    - Santa Cruz Art League.
      - Exhibit catalogs.
        - Copy / Copies., Fifth and sixth annual, 1932 - 1933 (Box 132, Folder 10)
    - Santa Paula Chamber of Commerce.
      - Exhibit catalogs.
        - Copy / Copies., 1943, 1948 - 1949 (Box 132, Folder 11)
          no. 7, 12 - 13
    - Various Associations Catalog Each.
      - Exhibit catalogs.
        - Copy / Copies., 1935 - 1957 (Box 132, Folder 12)
          Includes: Cannell Chaffin, Glendale Art Association, Stendahl Galleries, San Francisco Museum of Art, Santa Barbara Museum of Art, etc
    - Various Associations Each Outside California.
      - Exhibit catalogs.
        - Copy / Copies., ca. 1928 - 1950 (Box 132, Folder 13)
          Includes: Arizona State Fair, Pennsylvania Academy of the Fine Arts, St. Botolph Club (Boston), etc. Ca. 7 exhibits
    - Various Exhibits.
      - Exhibit materials.
        - Lists of items., 1930, 1944, no dates (Box 131, Folder 4)
          Includes list of Jake Zeitlin show (1930) and Raymond and Raymond show (1944, with "sold" annotations)
      - Post exhibit material.
        - Reviews. Clippings., 1927 (Box 132, Folder 14)
        - Reviews. Clippings., 1929 (Box 132, Folder 15)
        - Reviews. Clippings., 1930 (Box 132, Folder 16)
        - Reviews. Clippings., 1931 (Box 132, Folder 17)
        - Reviews. Clippings., 1932 (Box 132, Folder 18)
        - Reviews. Clippings., 1933 - 1936 (Box 132, Folder 19)
        - Reviews. Clippings., 1940 - 1942 (Box 132, Folder 20)
        - Reviews. Clippings., 1943 (Box 132, Folder 21)
          2 items. Los Angeles County Museum of Art one woman show
        - Reviews. Clippings., 1944 (Box 132, Folder 22)
        - Reviews. Clippings., 1944 (Box 132, Folder 24)